<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>122353</Id>
  <Name>Bentley</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>64379</Id>
    <Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name>
    <CityId>19793</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>500 EAST 62ND STREET</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>NEW YORK</City>
    <State />
    <Zip>10065</Zip>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>212-644-6000</Tel>
    <Fax />
    <Email>FIT@NYCHOTELS.COM</Email>
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>4</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>197</CountRooms>
    <CountFloors>21</CountFloors>
    <CountSuites>36</CountSuites>
    <Latitude>40.760153</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-73.958293</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>263</Height>
    <Bytes>15736</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Exterior</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2292</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_2.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>230</Height>
    <Bytes>18228</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Lobby</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>106</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>3174</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_3.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>233</Height>
    <Bytes>13165</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2235</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_4.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>226</Height>
    <Bytes>20963</Bytes>
    <Caption>Meeting Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/122353_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2775</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The Bentley is located on the fashionable Upper East Side of Manhattan, with its contemporary mix of art nouveau and deco styles. The Bentley Hotel overlooks the East River and 59th Street Bridge. The Bentley is located convenient to the world-famous shopping meccas, Blommingdale's and Barney's New York, which makes it a great choice for the visitor on a serious shopping mission. The 59th Street Bridge, an engineering marvel completed in 1909, provides a picture-perfect backdrop to this boutique hotel at the eastern edge of Manhattan’s Upper East Side. Witty decorative touches throughout the Bentley include a giant stainless-steel “vase” sculpture, a mobile-style chandelier with paper greetings in various languages, and room-number signs embellished with tiny artificial-flower bouquets. Foldout city and subway maps are attached to electronic room keys.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>• East River - 1 block
• Rockefeller University - 1 block
• Roosevelt Island Tram - 4 blocks
• Bloomingdale’s - 4 blocks
• Conran (renowned home-furnishings store) - 4 blocks
• Fifth Avenue - 6 blocks
• Central Park - 6 blocks
• Memorial Sloan-Kettering - 6 blocks
• New York Presbyterian Hospital - 6 blocks
• Tiffany &amp; Co - 11 blocks
• Broadway Theater District - 0.75 mile
• Rockefeller Center - 1 mile
• Radio City Music Hall - 1 mile
• United Nations - 1 mile
• Grand Central Terminal - 1 mile
• Chrysler Building - 1 mile
• Museum of Modern Art - 1 mile
• Empire State Building - 1.75 miles
• Times Square - 1.75 miles
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Guestrooms at this New York hotel feature custom-designed furniture, Belgian linens, and down comforters. Marble bathrooms offer shower/tub combinations, plush cotton towels, telephones, and British Gilchrist &amp; Soames toiletries. Wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge.
Other amenities include CD players, multi-line phones with voice mail, and cable TV with pay movies and video games (surcharge). Microwave ovens and compact refrigerators are available upon request; surcharges apply.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>Renovated in 2003, this 2-storey hotel comprises a total of 186 rooms of which 10 are suites. This attractive hotel is fully air-conditioned and facilities include a lobby with 24-hour reception, a cloakroom and lifts. This New York City hotel is one block from the East River, four blocks from Bloomingdale’s, and six blocks from Fifth Avenue and Central Park. Rockefeller Center, the Theater District, and the United Nations are within a mile. Two major hospitals—Memorial Sloan-Kettering and New York Presbyterian—are six blocks from the Bentley.
The hotel’s Rooftop Restaurant and Bar, open for dinner and drinks, is glass-enclosed on three sides to take advantage of bridge, river, and city views. The menu showcases American and Continental cuisine, including Veal Piccata, Penne Alla Vodka, and Flambéed Gin Steak. Fresh flowers, votive candles, and black tablecloths set a romantic mood. Seating is also available on the restaurant’s outdoor deck, weather permitting.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>AreaActivities</Type>
    <Text>• Ice skating
• Boat launch
• Tennis
• Running track/path
• Helicopter/airplane sightseeing
• Bird watching
• Fishing
• Playground
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type>
    <Text>All Major credit cards are accepted.
Check In Time - 3 p.m.
Check Out Time - 12 p.m.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DrivingDirections</Type>
    <Text>• From LaGuardia International Airport:
Take Grand Central Pkwy West to I-278 West. Exit SR-25A and bear right on Queens Plaza N. Stay on Queensboro Bridge to 2nd Ave S Exit. Turn left onto 2nd Ave, left onto E 59th St. Turn left onto 1st Ave, right onto E 62nd St.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>Rooftop Restaurant and Bar - Glass-enclosed on three sides, with sweeping views of river, bridge, and city. American and Continental menu, including Veal Marsala, Chicken Romano, Linguine Caprese. Romantic ambience with fresh flowers, votive candles, black tablecloths. Seasonal outdoor dining terrace. Open daily except Sunday for dinner and drinks.
The Bentley’s restaurant is open for dinner only. Many additional dining options are within the surrounding area. The Bridgemarket Food Emporium, located beneath the 59th Street Bridge about four blocks from the hotel, is a great choice for grab-and-go goodies.
Nearby restaurants:
• Ritz Diner
• Tramway Diner
• Bistro 61
• East River Café
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>Spacious; beautifully decorated suites are the trademark of the well-known Bentley This perfect vacation location has all the comforts you and your family look for
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>MeetingRooms</Code>
    <Text>Meeting rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Restaurant</Code>
    <Text>Restaurant</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>WheelchairAccess</Code>
    <Text>Wheelchair access</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Lobby</Code>
    <Text>Lobby</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>40</Score>
    <Description>Four star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>13</Rank>
</HotelElement>