<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>130027</Id>
  <Name>Hotel 373</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>64379</Id>
    <Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name>
    <CityId>19793</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>373 Fifth Avenue</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>New York</City>
    <State>New York</State>
    <Zip>10016</Zip>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>+1 212 213 3388</Tel>
    <Fax>+1 510 628 9023</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>3</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>0</CountRooms>
    <Latitude>40.749076</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-73.983693</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_8.jpg</Url>
    <Width>288</Width>
    <Height>288</Height>
    <Bytes>46582</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Exterior</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_8_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2245</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_5.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>350</Height>
    <Bytes>14131</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_5_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1575</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_6.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>233</Height>
    <Bytes>14268</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_6_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2344</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_4.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>350</Height>
    <Bytes>25791</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Interior</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/130027_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1944</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>Hotel 373 opened in 2007, this small, friendly hotel stands just one block from the Empire State Building. Hotel 373 is ideally situated in the heart of the Midtown area. The Lincoln Center, Madison Square Garden and Rockefeller Center are all located moments from the hotel's front doors. The Jacob Javits Center as well as the luxury shopping of Fifth Avenue are also within walking distance.In the lobby, sliding glass doors lead to a Starbucks coffee shop. Guests are mostly leisure travelers who appreciate the convenient Midtown location near shopping, dining, and world-famous attractions. A large, light-filled Starbucks, just off the lobby, is an ideal spot to jump-start the day or unwind after shopping and sightseeing.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>• Empire State Building - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi
• The Morgan Library and Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi
• Macy's - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi
• New York Public Library - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi
• Bryant Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi
• Madison Square Garden - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi
• Grand Central Terminal - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi
• Chrysler Building - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi
• Times Square - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi
• Broadway - 1 km / 0.6 mi
• Rockefeller Plaza - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi
• Central Park - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi
• Brooklyn Bridge - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi
• Ellis Island - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi
• Statue of Liberty - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Guestrooms feature wall-mounted LCD TVs with 150 channels, clock radios with iPod docking stations, and desks with ergonomic chairs. Beds come with down duvets and abundant pillows.Marble bathrooms offer walk-in showers (no tubs) with curved curtain rods for extra room. Wireless and wired high-speed Internet access are complimentary. Custom-made cherry-wood furniture provides a warm, contemporary look.Guestrooms have small, open closets or clothes hooks. Bathrobes are available upon request. All are non-smoking. As with many New York hotels, guestrooms are small but well-appointed.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>This Midtown hotel faces Fifth Avenue at West 35th Street. The Empire State Building is one block south, Macy's is a two-block stroll, and the elegant Lord &amp; Taylor department store, famed for its Christmas displays, is three blocks north. Times Square, Broadway theaters, and Grand Central Terminal are with a half-mile.A Starbucks off the lobby is open from early morning until late evening. Guests can also order delivery service from nearby restaurants, or take a short walk to a wide array of gourmet and casual dining options. The Hotel 373 Fifth Avenue is completely smoke-free.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DrivingDirections</Type>
    <Text>Directions From LaGuardia Airport:
1. Head Southwest 2. Turn left toward Grand Central Pkwy. W 3. Sharp right to merge onto Grand Central Pkwy W. 4. Take the exit onto Brooklyn Queens Expy W 5. Merge onto I-278 W 6. Take exit 35 for I-495 /L.I. Expy toward Midtown Tun/Eastern L.I./Greenpoint Ave 7. Merge onto I-495 W 8. Continue onto NY-495 W 9. Turn right at E 34th St 10. Turn right at Madison Ave 11. Turn left at the 3rd cross street onto E 37th St 12. Take the 1st left onto 5th Ave Destination will be on the left

Directions From JFK International Airport
1. Head northeast on Van Wyck Expy toward Van Wyck Expy 2. Slight left toward JFK Access Rd 3. Continue straight onto JFK Access Rd 4. Continue onto Van Wyck Expy 5. Continue onto I-678 N 6. Take exit 12B for I-495 W/L I Expy toward Midtown Tun 7. Merge onto I-495 W 8. Turn right at E 34th St 9. Turn right at Madison Ave 10. Turn left at the 3rd cross street onto E 37th St 11. Take the 1st left onto 5th Ave Destination will be on the left</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>Starbucks - Coffee, lattes, and other beverages, along with pastries and snacks. Accessible directly from lobby. Open daily from early morning till late evening.Hotel 373 Fifth Avenue does not have a restaurant, but guestrooms include a list of nearby restaurants that provide delivery service. Numerous dining options for all tastes and budgets are within walking distance.

Nearby restaurants:
• Villa Berulia
• Salmon River
• Benjamin Steakhouse
• Carmine's
• Monster Sushi
• Barbes</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>Sure to please any traveler; the Hotel 373 is proud to offer outstanding service and superior accommodations Amazing city views and city excitement in walking distance; we await your arrival
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>CoffeeShop</Code>
    <Text>Coffee shop</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>AirConditioned</Code>
    <Text>Air-conditioned</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Concierge</Code>
    <Text>Concierge</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code>
    <Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Elevators</Code>
    <Text>Elevators</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Lobby</Code>
    <Text>Lobby</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>30</Score>
    <Description>Three star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>