<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>143297</Id><Name>Bentley Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21302</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Halaskargazi cd. No: 75 Harbiye</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip>34367</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+902122917730</Tel><Fax>+902122917740</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>50</CountRooms><Latitude>41.050062</Latitude><Longitude>28.987499</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-front.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>2400</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-front_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2395</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-front.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>11019</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-front.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2001</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-room2.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>5759</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-room2.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1611</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-room.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>5308</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1031856-bentley-room.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1626</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>General information: The Bentley offers comfort and design, a relaxing environment and state-of-the-art information technologies, Bentley Hotel is the ideal spot for those who prefer not to give up their lifestyle while traveling. Our guests at Bentley Hotel have the privilege to live luxury in a modern and cozy environment. In a plain and peaceful atmosphere, comfort lays in the details tailored according to your needs.Location:Located at the hip Nisantasi area, famous for famous shops, coffees, restaurants, bars and night clubs. Bentley Hotel is meters away from the big convention center Lutfi Kirdar.Area details:At the intersection of Harbiye and Nisantasi, Bentley Hotel Istanbul is within walking distance to Istanbul’s popular restaurants, clubs, distinguished shopping area, as well as the Military Museum, Open-air Theatre, major concert halls, congress and exposition centers, travel agencies and the subway.On a business or leisure trip, this is the perfect hotel in Istanbul, which allows you to enjoy the comfort of being centrally located while enabling you to leave the buzz of the city behind you at the moment you step into the hotel.Recreation:The Restaurant offers both hotel and external guests the delights of a fusion cuisine, mixing traditional Turkish tastes with international classics.Enjoying a drink on a comforting, trendy atmosphere and distinguished interior design, in a the hotel’s Bar is one of the popular meeting spots of the city’s nightlife.A sauna and an equipped work out room offer guests the opportunity to relax and stay fit.Rooms:All rooms are decorated with a sleek and spare palate of white, beige, and black, which are the result of the Milanese minimalist design.Functionality and comfort are represented at the same time in these fully equipped rooms.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Beyond a pleasant stay, The Bentley Hotel offers guests the possibility to experience a particular lifestyle with all its components. With a blend of classic and contemporary and relaxing environment.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BarLounge</Code><Text>Bar/Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetLaundry</Code><Text>Valet Laundry</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>