<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>14718047</Id><Name>Cvk Hotels &amp; Resorts Park Bosphorus Istanbul</Name><Region><Id>21304</Id><Name>Taksim</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Gumussuyu Mah. Inonu Cad. 8 Istanbul</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State>Istanbul</State><Zip>34437</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+902 12 245 02 24</Tel><Fax /><Email>reservations@parkbosphorus.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>28.987588</Latitude><Longitude>41.03545</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQfront.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQthumbfront.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1654</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQbed.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQthumbbed.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1613</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/CJQthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1819</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>CVK Hotels &amp; Resorts Park Bosphorus - Istanbul is an elegant 5-star superior property offering luxury accommodation in the heart of Istanbul. Highlights include an indoor swimming pool with an opening apex, a fitness centre and a spa. Beyoglu is a vibrant cosmopolitan area across the Golden Horn from historic Constantinople. Traditionally home to European merchants and immigrants, it boasts many elegant Neoclassical and Art Nouveau structures. Nearby places of interest include the grand Taksim Square, medieval Galata Tower, modern art gallery Dogancay Museum and Istiklal Caddesi, a thriving street lined with cafes, bars, galleries and shops. Taksim tram and metro stations are located in the vicinity, providing fast and easy access to other popular Istanbul destinations. The hotel is housed in a complex consisting of elegant mid-rise buildings with light, white and beige facades. Facilities include an indoor swimming pool with an opening apex, traditional steam rooms, a fitness centre, a spa and a beauty salon. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Superior Sea rooms are spacious, bright and elegantly furnished. They are decorated in cool blue tones with light wood floors and boast stunning sea views. Amenities include air-conditioning, satellite TV, a work desk, a telephone, a mini-bar, tea and coffee equipment and a safe. The en-suite bathrooms feature a bathtub, TV and luxury toiletries. Miramare Restaurant serves Mediterranean cuisine in a chic, stylish setting and boasts a terrace with stunning views of the Bosphorus. Taksim Restaurant serves international buffet-style dishes in an open, contemporary setting. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks at the Blue Sky Bar &amp; Lounge in a lively, ambient environment. The hotel has a 24-hour reception. Chargeable parking is possible onsite.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>