<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>15259051</Id><Name>HILTON BOMONTI HOTEL &amp; CONFERENCE CENTER</Name><Region><Id>21302</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Silahsor Cd No 42 Bomonti Sisli  , Istanbul      Turkey</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+90 (212) 375 30 00</Tel><Fax>+90 (212) 375 30 01</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>0</Latitude><Longitude>0</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1854</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1785</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZmap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/EQZthumbmap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1589</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Hilton Istanbul Bomonti Hotel &amp; Conference Center is a luxury 5-star property offering contemporary accommodation near the heart of Istanbul. Highlights include indoor and outdoor swimming pools, a fitness centre and an excellent location opposite the former Bomonti Beer Factory. Sisli is a cosmopolitan residential area towards the north of European Istanbul. It developed in the late 19th and early 20th-centuries and features many modern structures alongside several impressive Art Nouveau buildings. Nearby places of interest include BJK Inonu Stadium and the huge shopping mall, Istanbul Cevahir. Osmanbey metro station is located in the vicinity, providing fast and easy access to other popular Istanbul destinations. The hotel is housed in a modern high-rise building with a minimalist, glass facade. Facilities include indoor and outdoor swimming pools, a fitness centre, a luxury spa, a sauna, a steam room and a beauty salon. Free Wi-Fi is available in public areas. Standard rooms are 35sqm, bright and airy featuring floor-to-ceiling windows. Amenities include air-conditioning, satellite TV, a mini-bar, tea and coffee equipment, a safe and a work desk. The en-suite bathrooms feature a bathtub and a hairdryer. Cloud 34 offers Turkish and international cuisine in a sophisticated and ambient setting. The Globe offers international dishes in a unique and interactive atmosphere and is open 24-hour a day. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks at elegant Grand Bar featuring chic leather decor, or the Grand Lobby with its large open-fireplace. A buffet breakfast is provided every morning. The hotel provides 24-hour reception and room service. Chargeable parking is possible onsite.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>