<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>15263301</Id><Name>NIDYA  HOTEL GALATAPORT</Name><Region><Id>21302</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Meclisi Mebusan Cd No:21 Tophane   , Istanbul      Turkey</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+90 (212) 292 90 60</Tel><Fax>+90 (212) 292 57 57</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.028743</Latitude><Longitude>28.986125</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6front.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6thumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2334</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6bed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6thumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1882</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6map.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/YN6thumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1861</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Nidya Hotel Galataport is an elegant 4-star property offering modern accommodation in the heart of Istanbul. Highlights include onsite dining, a gym, spa and an excellent location near the Istanbul Museum of Modern Art. Beyoglu is a vibrant cosmopolitan area across the Golden Horn from historic Constantinople. Traditionally home to European merchants and immigrants, it boasts many elegant Neoclassical and Art Nouveau structures. Nearby places of interest include the grand Taksim Square, medieval Galata Tower, modern art gallery Dogancay Museum and Istiklal Caddesi, a thriving street lined with cafes, bars, galleries and shops. Tophane tram stop is located in the vicinity, providing fast and easy access to other popular Istanbul destinations. The hotel is housed in a modern mid-rise building with a smart facade. Facilities include a gym, beauty salon and spa with a sauna, steam room and treatment rooms. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Standard rooms are decorated in a modern style with earth tones and patterned carpets. They feature views of the main terrace and garden and a sitting area with an armchair. Amenities include air-conditioning, a safe, mini-bar and flat-screen cable/satellite TV. The en-suite bathrooms feature a spacious walk-in shower. Mares Restaurant offers local and international cuisine in a modern dining room. Garden Cafe serves a range of dishes in a comfortable setting with decorative plants and a glass roof. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks and snacks at the 24-hour Lobby Bar. A buffet breakfast is provided every morning and there are plenty of dining opportunities in the vicinity. Free parking is possible onsite. The hotel has a 24-hour reception and offers a chargeable airport shuttle service.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>