<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>317925</Id>
  <Name>Gramercy Park Hotel</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>64377</Id>
    <Name>Soho - Chelsea</Name>
    <CityId>19793</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>2 Lexington Avenue</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>New York</City>
    <State>New York</State>
    <Zip>10010</Zip>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>+ 1 212 920 3300</Tel>
    <Fax>+ 1 212 673 5890</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>0</CountRooms>
    <Latitude>40.738546</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-73.985772</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>249</Width>
    <Height>350</Height>
    <Bytes>18895</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Entrance</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>49</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1573</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_2.jpg</Url>
    <Width>600</Width>
    <Height>290</Height>
    <Bytes>29395</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>144</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>3054</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_4.jpg</Url>
    <Width>600</Width>
    <Height>290</Height>
    <Bytes>26926</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>144</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>3150</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_5.jpg</Url>
    <Width>600</Width>
    <Height>290</Height>
    <Bytes>36318</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Lobby</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/317925_5_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>144</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>3107</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The Gramercy Hotel is situated within walking distance of Union Square, the SoHo neighbourhood and the unique shops and restaurants of the Nolita area. Art galleries, an exciting nightlife and public transport systems are also easily accessible. The Gramercy Park Hotel has a uniqueness and individuality that make it stand out from the crowd of New York hotels. Ian Schrager, who acquired the hotel in 2003, took 3 years and $200 million to completely redo the existing building, which first opened in 1925, and where Humphrey Bogart among other celebrities lived for two years just after marrying his first wife, Helen Menken.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>• Gramercy Park - 0 km / 0 mi
• Flatiron Building - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi
• Madison Square Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi
• Empire State Building - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi
• New York University - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi
• Madison Square Garden - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi
• Chrysler Building - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi
• Grand Central Terminal - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi
• Times Square - 2 km / 1.3 mi
• Broadway - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi
• Rockefeller Plaza - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi
• Brooklyn Bridge - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi
• Central Park - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi
• Ellis Island - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi
• Statue of Liberty - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Guestrooms and suites at this New York hotel blend Renaissance opulence with modern luxuries and state-of-the art technology. Beds indulge with 400-thread-count Italian linens, featherbeds, down duvets and pillows, jewel-toned velvet throws, and velvet headboards. Amenities include high-definition LCD TVs, DVD players, wireless Internet access (surcharge), and iPod docking stations. Guests can borrow iPods with custom-designed playlists from the front desk (deposit required). Mahogany bathrooms feature Italian Frette robes, invigorating massage showerheads and handheld showers, and toiletries from Allure magazine's annual "Best Of" list. Large desks come with hand-stitched leather tops and tapestry-upholstered chairs. Photos are curated from the renowned Magnum collection. English bars feature European crystal stemware. Minibars are stocked with gourmet goodies and libations selected by Ian Schrager. Fresh flowers add a charming touch in bedrooms and baths.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>This New York hotel is five blocks from Union Square and within a half-mile of Chelsea, the East Village, Greenwich Village, and Midtown Manhattan. The hotel's top priority is gracious, knowledgeable service. All of its concierges belong to the prestigious Les Clefs d'Or professional organization. The Roof Club is a destination unto itself, with indoor and outdoor dining, lush landscaping under a retractable roof, and commanding city views. The club is open year-round to hotel guests and members. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available throughout the Gramercy Park Hotel. A 24-hour fitness center features two spa-treatment rooms, cardio machines with individual TVs, and views of Gramercy Park.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type>
    <Text>Pets not allowed
Check-in time is 3 PM
Check-out time is 12 PM
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>• Maialino - Critically acclaimed Restauranteur, Danny Meyer, created a brand new authentic Italian Trattoria on the lobby level of the hotel with views of Gramercy Park. In the morning guests can enjoy the front bar area as a coffee bar; later it becomes a lively wine bar serving wine and everything from small plates of food to full dining options into late evening. Maialino offers breakfast, lunch, and dinner. The trattoria atmosphere features warm colors, wood planked floors, and wainscoting. Special events and celebrations for up to 20 can be scheduled for the restaurant's private dining room.

• Rose Bar - Ultra-seductive candlelit bar with woodburning fireplace, rose-and-crimson palette, original art by contemporary masters such as Cy Twombly, Andy Warhol, Julien Schnabel. Furnishings designed by Schnabel. Crimson-topped pool table with hand-burned edges. DJ entertainment. Classic and creative cocktails; Champagnes and wines by the glass. Signature drinks for both Rose and Jade bars include the Berry Bellini, Original Georgia Mint Julep, Spiced Mango Martini. Open nightly except Sunday. Reservations required for entrance after 9 PM.

• Jade Bar - Intimate bar featuring dramatic original art by Jean-Michel Basquiat and Julien Schnabel. Soaring ceiling, jade-green furnishings. Classic and creative cocktails; Champagnes and wines by the glass. Bar menu includes appetizers, main courses, desserts. Open nightly. Reservations required for entrance after 9 PM.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>Prime location; phenomenal customer service and luxury accommodations make the Gramercy Park Hotel the perfect choice Close to major attractions and city excitement; we invite you to be our guest</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>FitnessFacility</Code>
    <Text>Fitness facility</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>BusinessCenter</Code>
    <Text>Business center</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>RoomService</Code>
    <Text>Room service</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Restaurant</Code>
    <Text>Restaurant</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>BarLounge</Code>
    <Text>Bar/Lounge</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code>
    <Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>ValetLaundry</Code>
    <Text>Valet Laundry</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>