<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>3353296</Id><Name>Mangana Konak Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21303</Id><Name>Old City</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Oyuncu Cikmazi Sok. No: 18-20,</Address1><Address2>Sultanahmet</Address2><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip>34400</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>0090 212 638 17 37</Tel><Fax>00902126381742</Fax><Email>mangana@armagrandi.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2441</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1763</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/TravCo/48Mthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1587</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Mangana Konak is a friendly 4-star hotel offering all-suite accommodation in the historic heart of Istanbul. It boasts free Wi-Fi and a great location steps from the Bosphorus. Sultanahmet is the oldest part of city. Bordered by the waters of the Sea of Marmara and the Bosphorus, it is home to several of Istanbul's most famous and beautiful historic structures. Nearby places of interest include the stunning 6th-century Hagia Sophia, the Blue Mosque and the majestic Sultan Ahmet Square, which contains many monuments and statues and the ruins of the Hippodrome of Constantinople. Cankurtaran train station is located in the vicinity, providing fast and easy access to other popular Istanbul destinations. The hotel occupies a traditional low-rise property featuring a highly decorative, partly wooden facade with intricate detailing and an arched entrance. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Standard rooms are approximately 15-21sqm and decorated in a simple style with wood floors and light colour scheme. They boast garden or partial sea views. Amenities include air-conditioning, satellite TV and an en-suite bathroom. There is no restaurant onsite, but a buffet breakfast is provided every morning on the hotel terrace, which boasts stunning sea and city views. There are also plenty of dining opportunities in the vicinity. The hotel provides 24-hour reception and room service. Chargeable parking is possible nearby.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>