<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>4120438</Id>
  <Name>St. Pancras Renaissance London</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>52890</Id>
    <Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name>
    <CityId>52612</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>EUSTON ROAD</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>LONDON</City>
    <State />
    <Zip />
    <Country>UK - England</Country>
    <Tel>44-20-7841-3540</Tel>
    <Fax>44-20-7841-3579</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <Latitude>51.5267173</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-0.132659</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Exterior_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>250</Width>
    <Height>360</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Bar_Lounge_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>250</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Bar_Lounge_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Lobby_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>250</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Lobby_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Guest_Room_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>250</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Lobby_2.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>250</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LON-STPhotel_Lobby_2_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>After years of devoted restoration, the St Pancras Renaissance London Hotel is being hailed as London's most romantic building. Its glorious Gothic Revival metalwork, gold leaf ceilings, hand-stencilled wall designs and the grand staircase are as dazzling as the day Queen Victoria opened the hotel in 1873.Designed by Sir George Gilbert Scott to receive travellers through St Pancras Station, the former Midland Grand Hotel offered its guests a world of grandeur, luxury and fantasy behind its fairytale red facade. Innovations such as ascending rooms (elevators) and revolving doors heightened the sense of awe. Those doors will be spinning again, sweeping guests into a world where modern luxuries mingle with the extravagance of rail's golden age. The hotel will also house a 350 capacity ballroom, a private club, a barber's shop and luxury spa, to include a swimming pool and 7 treatment rooms. (0111AB)</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>Direct access from to the concourse of the newly restored St Pancras International Eurostar Terminal, Europe's gateway to London and the UK. With trains to all points north and south (to Gatwick and Luton Airports), six Underground lines and London's ring road on its doorstep, nowhere has the local, national and international transport connections of St Pancras.
St Pancras, the so-called White Cliffs of London, welcomes visitors from the European mainland, and there is nowhere better for their journeys into the UK to begin. From neighbouring King's
Cross, high-speed trains serve the north and east of England, and Scotland. There are rapid rail links through London and to southern England. Six Undergound Lines, offer links to every part of
the capital, and direct connections to Covent Garden, Knightsbridge, Oxford Circus, the City, the West End, Waterloo, Paddington Station with the direct trains to Heathrow Airport, Liverpool Street Station with the direct trains to Stansted Airport. And for those travelling by car or taxi, Euston Road
is a great place to start getting around London. Regent's Park and Madame Tussauds are both a short bus or underground journey away.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Elegant and spacious Victorian bedrooms, with a combination of original features and contemporary design. General Room Amenities; Air conditioning, Alarm clock, Coffee maker/tea service, Individual climate control 
Iron and ironing board, Luxurious bedding down comforters, custom duvets, cotton rich linens, pillows: feather or foam and Safe. Bathroom Amenities; Bathrobe, slippers, Hair dryer, Separate tub and shower, Lighted makeup mirror. Room Entertainment; Flat Screen TV with Cable channels, satellite TV and Movies/videos, pay-per-view. Business Amenities; wired and wireless Internet (for a fee) Electrical outlet, desk level and chair, Phone feature: voice mail.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>High Victorian Gothic architecture in its most dramatic sense, the stunning redbrick building having been saved from demolition in the sixties by a protest led by former Poet Laureate Sir John Betjeman. Preserving the glamour of the old station and the romance of rail travel during the 1800s, the St Pancras Renaissance Hotel in London will maintain its elegance and charm by offering global travellers a gateway to London in the form of one of the city's greatest landmarks.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>The Gilbert Scott Two-Michelin-starred Restaurant, to be run by one of Britain's most celebrated chefs, Marcus Wareing. Featuring an exquisite David Collins designed interior that perfectly complements the stunning Victorian Gothic architecture of the iconic building. Set in the heart of the historic building and occupying the original entrance hall and coffee room, the restaurant is sure to become one of the most desirable dining and bar destinations in the Capital. The menu, will offer a unique take on British classics and the team will be led by Marcus' protege Chantelle Nicholson who will be taking the role of General Manager. Guests can continue to re-live the glamour of the Victorian era also at The Booking Office Bar &amp; Restaurant recreated in the original ticket office. A striking setting for a breakfast, snack or classic English dining from an all-day menu serving traditional fare, sumptuously updated, and a bar with its own take on classic English mixology.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>The infamous sweeping forecourt, unique to a London hotel in its size and presence, provides a fitting entrance for the new hotel that will also showcase restored gold-leaf ceilings, ornate wall murals and the spectacular grand staircase.  The famous staircase, widely revered as the most majestic in England with windows measuring over 50 feet and crowned by an elaborate vaulted ceiling,</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Sauna</Code>
    <Text>Sauna</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>AirConditioning</Code>
    <Text>Air conditioning</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>HairDryer</Code>
    <Text>Hair dryer</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>CarRentDesk</Code>
    <Text>Car rental desk</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>CarPark</Code>
    <Text>Car parking</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Gym</Code>
    <Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code>
    <Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>