<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>4983301</Id>
  <Name>Millennium Plaza Hotel Dubai</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>9043418</Id>
    <Name>Sheikh Zayed Road / Downtown</Name>
    <CityId>18870</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>P. O. BOX 191055, SHEIKH ZAYED ROAD</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>DUBAI</City>
    <State />
    <Zip />
    <Country>UNITED ARAB EMIRATES</Country>
    <Tel>0097143877777</Tel>
    <Fax>0097143877778</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <Latitude>25.217526</Latitude>
    <Longitude>55.278305</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/6/22Jfront.jpg</Url>
    <Width>400</Width>
    <Height>400</Height>
    <Bytes>111106</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/22Jthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1636</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/6/22Jbed.jpg</Url>
    <Width>400</Width>
    <Height>400</Height>
    <Bytes>112761</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/22Jthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2018</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/6/22Jmap.JPG</Url>
    <Width>400</Width>
    <Height>400</Height>
    <Bytes>43208</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/22Jthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1799</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The Millennium Plaza Hotel Dubai is a luxury 5-star property, offering stylish accommodation in Dubai's financial centre. The hotel features a rooftop swimming pool, a modern fitness centre and luxurious spa facilities, as well as top-class drinking and dining options. The hotel is located on the prominent Sheikh Zayed Road, where ultra-modern towers and skyscrapers grace the skyline. The location is ideal for leisure or business travellers. It is also within easy reach of the awe-inspiring Jumeirah beach, where guests can find pristine white sand and a wide variety of shopping and dining opportunities. Dubai International airport is also close by. The hotel is housed in a stunning 65-storey tower, which overlooks Sheikh Zayed Road, Zabeel Palace, Dubai creek and Jumeirah beach. Guests have private access to the swimming pool, health club and spa, which are located on the rooftop of the parking building. Guests can relax in the sauna and steam rooms, or enjoy soothing massages and other pampering treatments on request. Whether they desire a mid-noon break or a late-night dinner, guests are catered for in the tea lounge and the all-day restaurant. The menus cater for both Eastern and Western tastes. The air-conditioned Superior rooms offer a wide variety of amenities, including a 32-inch LCD TV, a DVD player, Jacuzzi, a hairdryer, a mini-bar, tea and coffee making facilities and a safe. Wi-Fi is also available. Parking is available onsite.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>