<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>5297587</Id>
  <Name>Shore Hotel</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>21625</Id>
    <Name>Santa Monica - Beach Cities</Name>
    <CityId>19704</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>1515 Ocean Avenue</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>Santa Monica</City>
    <State>CA</State>
    <Zip>90401</Zip>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>(310) 458-1515</Tel>
    <Fax>(310) 943-1510</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>4</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <Latitude>34.0124276</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-118.4961116</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>This is Santa Monica's new green and luxurious beachfront hotel. Shore Hotel is proud to be the first and only newly constructed LEED registered hotel in Santa Monica. Inspired by the convergence of Southern California's spectacular natural landscape with a unique urban fabric, Shore Hotel is the destination of choice among oceanfront hotels. A short walk from many attractions and just steps from the beach, Shore Hotel's location on Ocean Avenue allows visitors to effortlessly enjoy endless sunshine and a range of activities year-round.
The ocean, the sun and spectacular views are waiting. Unwind and settle in to one of the chic and comfortable guest rooms that feature a unique glass shower facing the ocean with a one-touch privacy screen. Put your mind at ease knowing that you can relax at Santa Monica's most environmentally conscious hotel. A stay in one of Shore Hotel's guest rooms provides the perfect balance of style and natural beauty. Each of the spacious guest rooms boasts exquisite views, private balconies, and all the comforts of home. Built with sustainable and environmentally friendly materials, the guest rooms feature the latest in distinctive California modern design and technology. When you stay at Shore Hotel, you will know you have indulged in Santa Monica's newest grand beachfront experience.
 

Facility Includes :
- Self Parking is $30 &amp; Valet Parking is $34 (fees subject to change)
- 164 guest rooms/ 4 floors
- 39 Garden view/ 15 Partial Ocean View
- Complimentry wired &amp; wireless internet access 
- Rain shower with one touch privacy screen
- Fully Stocked Minibar
- iHome 
- 37" Flat screen LCD HDTV
- Laptop Safe
- Iron and Ironing board
- Hairdryer
- Plush Bathrobes
- Coffee/Tea Maker
- Outdoor heated pool 
- 24-hour state of the art fitness center
- 24-hour business center
- Blue Plate Taco</Text>
  </Description>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>40</Score>
    <Description>Four star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>