<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>59129</Id>
  <Name>Mandalay Bay Resort</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>21611</Id>
    <Name>The Strip</Name>
    <CityId>19680</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>3950 Las Vegas Boulevard South</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>Las Vegas</City>
    <State>Nevada</State>
    <Zip>89119</Zip>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>1-702-632-7777</Tel>
    <Fax>17026327108</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>0</CountRooms>
    <Latitude>36.092767</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-115.176576</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>266</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Recreational_Facilities_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>241</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Recreational_Facilities_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Suite_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Suite_2.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-MAN1hotel_Suite_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The property features two hotel towers that operate as two separate hotels under the umbrella of one resort. The hotel at Mandalay Bay opened in December 2003, adding 1,117 all-suites to the overall resort. Both hotels have earned the prestigious Four Diamond Award from the American Automobile Association (AAA), recognizing the resort for its exception degree of hospitality, service and attention to detail.
Mandalay Bay's signature attraction is the 11 acres Mandalay Bay Beach, providing the ultimate in aquatic relaxation. This world famous playground offers a wave pool, lazy river, three swimming pools, jogging track and 2,700 tons of real sand. A recent $30 million expansion brought to The Beach more premium seating and the exclusive new Beachside Casino.The hotel has 135,000 square feet of gaming space.
Shop till you drop at Mandalay Place, with more than 40 unique boutique and restaurants. Take a break at the aquarium and view fascinating ocean species. A full-service luxury spa and fitness centre is available. A legendary House of Blues Music Hall is housed here, and the permanent production of Mamma Mia is in the showroom. Further entertainment is provided at the 12,000 seat special-events center and the 1,700 seat state-of-the-art theatre. The hotel has the largest convention and meeting facilities in Vegas. A wedding chapel is available.The bathhouse spa at THEhotel at Mandalay Bay includes a fitness center with personal training and yoga, a redwood sauna, spa tubs, a eucalyptus steam room, and an extensive menu of spa treatments.One of the attractions that will draw travelers initially to THEhotel, and will undoubtedly entice them to return is BATHHOUSE, and on-site, state of the art spa, like no other in Las Vegas. Much of its menu has been specifically designed resulting in a program of treatments and products unrivaled anywhere in Las Vegas.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>Mandalay Bay Resort &amp; Casino is a luxury destination resort set on 60 acres on the Las Vegas Strip. Tropically themed with mystical architecture and lush surroundings, Mandalay Bay offers an exciting, elegant experience for Las Vegas visitors.The resort is about a mile away from McCarran International Airport and the par-72 Bali Hai Golf Club.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>The new room designs of Mandalay Bay set a new standard in accommodation. Combining understated elegance with modern-day conveniences, each room type assures a perfect night's rest with pillow-top mattresses. Ranging in size from 550 to 1,500 square feet. A perfect night's sleep-that's what was sought to create with the newly remodeled Mandalay Bay rooms and suites. The theme here is casual elegance and comfort. Lofty pillow topped beds, triple high-thread count sheets, warm textiles in pleasing tones and 42" plasma TVs create the perfect environment for effortless relaxation or sweet dreams.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>This is a striking modern 43-storey resort, with gold glass windows, set on 60 acres, including an 11-acre tropical beach. Beautiful landscaping surrounds the hotel, including a myriad of palm trees.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>The restaurants of the hotel are a combination of eclectic menus, famous names and spectacular settings. Featuring the finest international cuisine and restaurateurs, here you will explore an unprecedented level of taste and quality in everything from elaborately sumptuous suppers to simple snacks prepared with a gesture of elegance.Fleur by Hubert Keller offers small plates from around the world featuring intense flavors and exotic presentations in a fun, social environment. Fleur offers casual seating at the bar, lounge and patio as well as a more intimate experience in our stunning dining room.Mix in Las Vegas - Located on the hotel's 43rd floor, Alain Ducasse's modern restaurant and lounge provides views of the Vegas hills and the Strip. French and American cuisine with global accents is served for dinner only. Lupo- by Wolfgang Puck's - restaurant offers an inviting atmosphere infused with a combination of turn-of-the-century antique furnishings, eye-catching colors and a clean design giving the restaurant the classic look and feel of a traditional Italian trattoria. The restaurant boasts exhibition pizza, antipasto and dessert stations, a glass-enclosed area where fresh pasta is made daily and a wine room that is surrounded by a spacious bar in the center of the restaurant.Red Square restaurant - Russian restaurant ,offers an impressive caviar selection,Siberian Nachos, Roquefort Filet Mignon, Strozapretti Stroganoff, Salmon Kulebyaka and Certified Angus Rib Eye.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>The large, luxurious lobby features high ceilings, marbled floors extending to the rest of the hotel and an amazing eye-catching aquarium.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Parking</Code>
    <Text>Parking</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Safe</Code>
    <Text>Safe</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>FitnessFacility</Code>
    <Text>Fitness facility</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>BusinessCenter</Code>
    <Text>Business center</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>RoomService</Code>
    <Text>Room service</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Restaurant</Code>
    <Text>Restaurant</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Lounge</Code>
    <Text>Lounge</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Concierge</Code>
    <Text>Concierge</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Hottub</Code>
    <Text>Hot Tub</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Giftshop</Code>
    <Text>Gift Shop</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Spa</Code>
    <Text>Spa</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Tours</Code>
    <Text>Tours</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Reception24Hour</Code>
    <Text>24 hour reception</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>ValetLaundry</Code>
    <Text>Valet Laundry</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>WheelchairAccess</Code>
    <Text>Wheelchair access</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>54</Rank>
</HotelElement>