<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>61778</Id>
  <Name>Excalibur</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>21611</Id>
    <Name>The Strip</Name>
    <CityId>19680</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>3850 LAS VEGAS BLVD. SOUTH LAS VEGAS NEVADA 89109</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>UNITED STATES</City>
    <State />
    <Zip />
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <Tel>1-702-5977777</Tel>
    <Fax>1-702-5977009</Fax>
    <Email />
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>3</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <Latitude>36.098909</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-115.175557</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>239</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>281</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Exterior_2.png</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>238</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Exterior_2_thumb.png</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Ballroom_1.png</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>284</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Ballroom_1_thumb.png</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Lobby_1.png</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>271</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Lobby_1_thumb.png</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>271</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_3.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>271</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_4.jpg</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>270</Height>
    <Bytes>0</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-EXC1hotel_Guest_Room_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The Excalibur is perfect for families because they can let their young ones act like knights and fair ladies. The Fun Dungeon is among the themed activities. It's packed with carnival-style games and a variety of 4-D rides. For example, in "SpongeBob SquarePants 4-D," kids can follow along with the lovable yellow sponge as he tracks down a missing pickle. The expansive pool area has a thrilling waterslide -- as well as 17 decked-out cabanas for parents. After dark, everyone can attend the "Tournament of Kings," where they'll experience the gallantry and equestrian feats from one of the tales about King Arthur. The arena is spectacular, and in addition to cheering on your knight, there is a three-course dinner to be eaten with your fingers.
Only a fabled resort can bring you dining beyond the ordinary. For gourmet fare, the Excalibur features The Steakhouse at Camelot. A Zagat Award winner, this steakhouse prepares fine cuts of beef, fresh seafood and decadent desserts. Enjoy Old World hospitality and family-style service at the beloved Italian restaurant chain Buca di Beppo. All ages can indulge in the bountiful Excalibur Buffet or enjoy quick, casual meals in ABX: American Burger Works and the sprawling Village Food Court, which is located in the Castle Walk shopping promenade.
The over-21 crowd will have a blast at the Excalibur's newest arrival -- Lynyrd Skynyrd BBQ &amp; Beer, where they can savor ribs, brisket and pulled pork washed down with a wide assortment of beers on tap. In a setting reminiscent of a backwoods shack, this quirky eatery houses a concert stage where live rock music reigns supreme. Dick's Last Resort is another alternative for nightlife-loving visitors. The bar and stage are always rocking in there as well, and when guests get hungry they can turn to a menu of pub grub complete with Macho Nachos, Mumbo Jumbo Chicky Wings and the Big Ass Burger. Or spend a high-energy night in the Octane Lounge, a classic rock bar with a display of custom-designed motorcycles. Among the signature drinks are the Blood, Sweat &amp; Gears Cosmo and the High Octane Kiss, served by bartenders dressed in black leather.
Blackjack and Megabucks are some of the gaming options the Excalibur will tempt you to try. In addition to the expansive casino, this family-friendly hotel showcases a nightly Tournament of Kings dinner show and the Fantasy Faire Midway, a carnival-themed arcade. The lively Tournament of Kings is a period-authentic jousting show complete with swordplay and dancing. This entertainment is unique to the Excalibur.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>Located on the best corner of the famed Las Vegas strip, Excalibur is the ideal property for value and variety. Excalibur offers everything you'd expect from a Las Vegas hotel - elegant and casual dining, a first class spa, thrilling entertainment and non-stop friendly Las Vegas casino action. It's the perfect place to relax and prepare for your next adventure.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>The Tower rooms feature warm, comforting tones and hardwood furnishings, high-speed Internet access, cable TV, hair dryers, and irons. Tower rooms have either one king or two queen-sized beds.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>This is a Camelot-inspired hotel that is comprised of four castle towers featuring storybook-style castle gates, a moat, multicolor spires and a modified medieval theme.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>The Steakhouse at Camelot - Contemporary steakhouse serving prime-grade beef and fresh seafood. Subdued lighting. Glassed-in show kitchen. Wine/cigar room. Piano lounge. Dinner only. 
Dick's Last Resort - Burgers, barbecue, seafood, and more served in buckets and accompanied with bibs and hats. Live music. Open daily for lunch and dinner. 
Additionally, an ever-popular dinner show comes complete with jousting kings, invading armies, maidens and regal celebrations, all while you enjoy a banquet meal with your hands! 24-hour room service is also available.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>The rather large lobby is part of the main casino area, situated on the left side of the entrance. It is long and narrow, with many check-in counters.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>OutdoorPool</Code>
    <Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>AirConditioning</Code>
    <Text>Air conditioning</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>HairDryer</Code>
    <Text>Hair dryer</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>CarRentDesk</Code>
    <Text>Car rental desk</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code>
    <Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>TrouserPress</Code>
    <Text>Trouser press</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Shops</Code>
    <Text>Shops</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>30</Score>
    <Description>Three star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>