<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>717151</Id>
  <Name>Aria Resort &amp; Casino</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>21611</Id>
    <Name>The Strip</Name>
    <CityId>19680</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>3730 LAS VEGAS BOULEVARD SOUTH</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>Las Vegas (NV)</City>
    <State />
    <Zip>89158</Zip>
    <Country>UNITED STATES</Country>
    <Tel>+1 702-590-7111</Tel>
    <Fax>+1 702 590 9723</Fax>
    <Email>ariawhlse@arialasvegas.com</Email>
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>4004</CountRooms>
    <CountFloors>61</CountFloors>
    <Latitude>36.107635</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-115.176722</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>343</Width>
    <Height>360</Height>
    <Bytes>39653</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2603</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>281</Height>
    <Bytes>17309</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1944</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_2.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>257</Height>
    <Bytes>16281</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1956</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Spa_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>13370</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Spa_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1807</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Restaurant_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>23157</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2333</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Other_1.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>248</Height>
    <Bytes>15695</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Other_1_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2033</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Restaurant_2.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>240</Height>
    <Bytes>20729</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Restaurant_2_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2348</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_3.bmp</Url>
    <Width>360</Width>
    <Height>257</Height>
    <Bytes>14550</Bytes>
    <Caption />
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-ARI4hotel_Guest_Room_3_thumb.bmp</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1879</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>The resort features a variety of dining experiences, from the casual comfort of bistros and cafes to culinary masterpieces. Guests will also enjoy ARIA's dynamic collection of lounges, bars and nightclubs. For a day of relaxation, ARIA's luxurious spa will offer a complete menu of skincare, massage and hydrotherapy treatments to be enjoyed in its 62 individual treatment rooms or three spa suites, designed to accommodate couples treatments, bachelorette parties, or small group events. Guests also may savor a quiet moment on the spa's co-ed balcony overlooking the resort's beautiful pools. The spa will be complemented by the resort's full service salon, barbershop, deluxe fitness room and group exercise studio.ARIA's 4,004 guest rooms will incorporate integrated technologies never before used in the hospitality industry. Guest room corridors streaming with natural light will open to areas of enclosed glass, delivering spectacular city or mountain views. Guests can also enjoy these breathtaking views from the privacy of their own rooms as all rooms feature expansive floor to ceiling windows</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>Located right in the center of the strip in the new City Center a collection of upscale shopping, dining and art venues.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Averaging 520 square feet, the Deluxe Room features an array of amenities and contemporary custom furnishings along with the world's most innovative in-room technology with one-touch controls allowing you to set each of your room's exclusive features to your personal standards. Amenities include entry foyer, dressing area with dual closets and granite top dresser, twice daily housekeeping service, custom ARIA mattress with triple-sheeted, 300 thread count linens, plush robes, stocked mini-bar, 42" LCD HD television that allows you to connect your laptop, control room automation and plug in video devices, such as game consoles, cameras or MP3 players, Integrated one-touch control of room features, including dimmable lighting, room temperature, television/video systems, music, wake-up calls, draperies, and requests for services through a single, easy-to-use remote control, bedside, 7" touch-screen technology also allows for easy navigation of room settings, workstation with high-speed, wireless and wired Internet connections and a laptop size in-rom safe. Bathroom Amenities: 100% cotton bath linens, shower with bench adjacent to a soaking tub, granite dual sink vanity, private water closet</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>Stunning modern high rise.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>ARIA has assembled a collection of the world's most critically acclaimed chefs and restaurateurs, with enticing new concepts from such chefs as Jean-Georges Vongerichten, Michael Mina, Sirio Maccioni, and Julian Serrano. 
Bar Masa - Chef Masayoshi Takayama's restaurant concept features two distinct dining experiences. The restaurant's casual dining space offers an a la carte menu of modern Japanese cuisine. Shaboo, the intimate and exclusive venue within Bar Masa, serves an ever-changing menu based on the best seasonally available ingredients. Each table features its own induction cooking element. 
American Fish - The bounty of American lakes, rivers, and coasts create the menu at Chef Michael Mina's restaurant. Many products are purchased directly from fishermen, farmers, and ranchers, allowing diners to enjoy regional dishes. The menu also features an array of well-sourced meats. 
Julian Serrano - The chef's restaurant offers a casual atmosphere with menus at different price points. An expansive seafood bar highlights fresh shellfish and ceviches, while the dining room and lounge serve tapas and other dishes from Serrano's native Spain. 
Jean-Georges Steakhouse - Chef Jean-Georges Vongerichten melds steakhouse touches with a contemporary experience. The menu offers an innovative array of side dishes and sauces, while the restaurant's lounge and bar focus on classic cocktails. 
Sirio Ristorante - Chef Sirio Maccioni's dining experience offers a menu of Italian favorites such as Veal Milanese, Osso Buco, and authentic pasta dishes. Guests can enjoy traditional cocktails of Italy and one of Las Vegas' largest selections of Italian vintages. 
JP Patisserie - Offering signature chocolates and desserts by Chef Jean-Philippe Maury, as well as breakfast pastries, sandwiches, crepes, salads, and paninis.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>Short</Type>
    <Text>From the soaring three-story lobby to the naturally lit casino, ARIA evokes openness and freedom. Art and interior design will greet guests in warm, comforting surroundings and provide a sense of human scale</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>InRoomMovies</Code>
    <Text>In-room movies</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>FitnessFacility</Code>
    <Text>Fitness facility</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>BusinessCenter</Code>
    <Text>Business center</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code>
    <Text>Mini-bar</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>HairDryer</Code>
    <Text>Hair dryer</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>AirConditioned</Code>
    <Text>Air-conditioned</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code>
    <Text>Private bathrooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Shower</Code>
    <Text>Shower</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>SatelliteTV</Code>
    <Text>Satellite TV</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>InternetAccess</Code>
    <Text>InternetAccess</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code>
    <Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Giftshop</Code>
    <Text>Gift Shop</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Tours</Code>
    <Text>Tours</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>HotelSafe</Code>
    <Text>Central hotel safe</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>TrouserPress</Code>
    <Text>Trouser press</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>*FB plus</Code>
    <Text>*FB plus</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>HotelPetsNotAllowed</Code>
    <Text>Hotel Pets NotAllowed</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Room220V</Code>
    <Text>Room 220V</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>RoomToiletries</Code>
    <Text>Room Toiletries</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>105</Rank>
</HotelElement>