<?xml version="1.0"?>
<HotelElement>
  <Id>721786</Id>
  <Name>Mandarin Oriental</Name>
  <Region>
    <Id>64379</Id>
    <Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name>
    <CityId>19793</CityId>
  </Region>
  <Type>Hotel</Type>
  <Address>
    <Address1>80 COLUMBUS CIRCLE AT 60TH ST</Address1>
    <Address2 />
    <Address3 />
    <City>New York (NY)</City>
    <State />
    <Zip>10023</Zip>
    <Country>UNITED STATES</Country>
    <Tel>+1 212 805 8800</Tel>
    <Fax>+1 212 313 9806</Fax>
    <Email>vipconcierge@alliedtpro.com</Email>
    <Url />
  </Address>
  <Stars>5</Stars>
  <GeneralInfo>
    <CountRooms>248</CountRooms>
    <CountFloors>18</CountFloors>
    <Latitude>40.7679499</Latitude>
    <Longitude>-73.9823617</Longitude>
  </GeneralInfo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_1.jpg</Url>
    <Width>288</Width>
    <Height>288</Height>
    <Bytes>25659</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Exterior</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1876</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_3.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>233</Height>
    <Bytes>19311</Bytes>
    <Caption>Guest Room</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2895</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_5.jpg</Url>
    <Width>233</Width>
    <Height>350</Height>
    <Bytes>23595</Bytes>
    <Caption>Hotel Lobby</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_5_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>1653</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Photo>
    <Url>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_4.jpg</Url>
    <Width>350</Width>
    <Height>233</Height>
    <Bytes>20946</Bytes>
    <Caption>Swimming Pool</Caption>
    <ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/Hotel/721786_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl>
    <ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth>
    <ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight>
    <ThumbnailBytes>2954</ThumbnailBytes>
    <PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType>
  </Photo>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>General</Type>
    <Text>Mandarin Oriental, Gaze over Central Park and the Manhattan skyline from the most breathtaking luxury hotel in New York. This award-winning, 5 Star development high above Columbus Circle offers stunning views from every room. In the beating heart of the city, close to the most prestigious areas, Mandarin Oriental, New York has become a byword for New York style.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>SurroundingArea</Type>
    <Text>• Time Warner Center - 0.1 km / 0 mi
• Carnegie Hall - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi
• Metropolitan Opera House - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi
• New York Public Library for the Performing Arts - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi
• Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi
• Rockefeller Plaza - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi
• Broadway - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi
• Times Square - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi
• Grand Central Terminal - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi
• Chrysler Building - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi
• Empire State Building - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi
• Central Park - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi
• Brooklyn Bridge - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi
• Ellis Island - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi
• Statue of Liberty - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>RoomTypes</Type>
    <Text>Located in the north high-rise of the Time Warner Center, this New York luxury hotel offers guestrooms on floors 38–54. All have floor-to-ceiling windows with expansive views of Central Park, the Hudson River, the Manhattan skyline, or other city sights. Binoculars are provided. Rooms have stylish, 1940s-inspired cherry-wood furniture and Asian-inspired palettes of Chinese red and silver, or jet-black and pale gold. Bedding includes custom Italian Fili D’oro brand Egyptian-cotton linens. The home-theater experience includes a 36-inch, flat-panel, high-definition TV with approximately 100 channels; surround sound stereo; and CD and DVD players with complimentary CD/DVD library. Rooms offer wireless, high-speed, and TV-based Internet access (surcharges), and three multiline phones. In-room safes and stocked minibars are standard amenities.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PropertyInformation</Type>
    <Text>The Mandarin Oriental is part of the Time Warner Center, which also contains luxury condominiums, entertainment venues, offices, and the Shops at Columbus Circle with 50 upscale retailers. Throughout the hotel, contemporary design and technology blend with an Asian aesthetic. Antique Mandarin silk robes are displayed on walls, ginkgo-leaf motifs accent the light-filled public spaces, and bamboo floors and bubbling waters create serenity in the spa. Modern artworks by Dale Chihuly and Valerio Adami highlight the lobbies and lounge. Wondrous views of the city abound.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>AreaActivities</Type>
    <Text>• Golfing
• Golf - driving range
• Golf - miniature
• Ice skating
• Rowing or canoeing
• Boating
• Swimming on site
• Tennis
• Running track/path
• Basketball
• Aerobics
• Pilates classes/instruction
• Yoga classes/instruction on site
• Hiking/biking trails
• Bicycle rentals
• Horse riding/rental
• Helicopter/airplane sightseeing
• Bird watching
• Fishing
• Playground
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type>
    <Text>Check-in time is 3 PM
Check-out time is Noon
Dogs only
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DrivingDirections</Type>
    <Text>From Kennedy Airport
• Exit Kennedy Airport, following signs to “New York City-Van Wyck Expressway”
• Follow Van Wyck Expressway, until Exit 10 for “Grand Central Parkway-Triboro Bridge”
• Continue upon the Grand Central Parkway, following signs to the Robert F. Kennedy Bridge -Crossing the bridge, remain to the right side for access to Manhattan, following signs to “FDR Drive – South”
• PAY TOLL when exiting the Robert F. Kennedy Bridge -Access the FDR Drive – South, exiting (on right side) at 63rd Street -After exiting, cross through traffic light and continue upon 63rd Street, until Fifth Avenue -Make a left turn onto Fifth Avenue, remaining on the right side until 60th Street -Right turn onto 60th Street -Right turn onto Central Park South, to Columbus Circle -Upon entering the circle, follow Columbus Circle until entering Broadway (Second major Avenue to the right) Note: You will notice a large silver Globe located to the right of Broadway -Immediately upon entering Broadway, make the first left onto 60th Street (at first traffic light) -Mandarin Oriental New York is located immediately on your left side on 60th Street between Broadway and Columbus Avenue.</Text>
  </Description>
  <Description>
    <Language>en</Language>
    <Type>DiningFacilities</Type>
    <Text>• Asiate - Central Park and Manhattan skyline vistas from 35th-floor perch. Floor-to-ceiling wall of wine collection of 1,300 bottles. Tree-branch ceiling sculpture of glass infused with mercury, evoking trees of Central Park. French-Japanese fusion cuisine. Six-course tasting menu, pre-theater menu. Daily breakfast and dinner; lunch Monday–Friday; brunch Saturday-Sunday. Dinner reservations recommended.
• Mandarin Oriental Lobby Lounge - Floor-to-ceiling windows framing spectacular views of Central Park. Striking modern art by Valerio Adami. Butterscotch-yellow seating. Railing accented with ginkgo-motif tooled silver. Appetizers, light fare, afternoon tea service, cocktails. Open from late morning to late evening.
• MObar - Stylish gathering place adjoining lobby. Hammered-nickel bar, custom leather seating with carved-stone backs. Cocktails and light fare served. Open from late afternoon to late evening.
Room service - Available 24 hours.
</Text>
  </Description>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code>
    <Text>Non smoking rooms</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>FitnessFacility</Code>
    <Text>Fitness facility</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>BusinessCenter</Code>
    <Text>Business center</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>AirConditioning</Code>
    <Text>Air conditioning</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>RoomService</Code>
    <Text>Room service</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Restaurant</Code>
    <Text>Restaurant</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Lift</Code>
    <Text>Lift</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code>
    <Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Spa</Code>
    <Text>Spa</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>SwimmingPool</Code>
    <Text>Swimming pool</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Reception24Hour</Code>
    <Text>24 hour reception</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Amenity>
    <Code>Elevators</Code>
    <Text>Elevators</Text>
  </Amenity>
  <Rating>
    <System>Stars</System>
    <Score>50</Score>
    <Description>Five star</Description>
  </Rating>
  <Rank>1</Rank>
</HotelElement>