<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="372672663_88033"><Hotel id="88033" name="Helvetia Deluxe Hotel" type="Hotel" stars="4" rank="20"><Region id="18149" name="St Petersburg" /><Address><Address1>11 Marata Street</Address1><Address2 /><City>St Petersburg</City><State /><Zip>191025</Zip><Country>Russian Federation</Country><Tel>7-812-3265353</Tel><Fax>7-812-3262009</Fax></Address><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LED-HEL2hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>248</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LED-HEL2hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LED-HEL2hotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LED-HEL2hotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Helvetia Hotel places you in the heart of St. Petersburg, walking distance from Arctic and Antarctic Museum and Dostoyevsky Museum.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Microminiature Museum and Galeria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 75 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and express check-in. Planning an event in St. Petersburg? This hotel has 699 square feet (65 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. A shuttle from the airport to the hotel is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 75 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Helvetia Hotel places you in the heart of St. Petersburg, walking distance from Arctic and Antarctic Museum and Dostoyevsky Museum.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Microminiature Museum and Galeria. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Arctic and Antarctic Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dostoyevsky Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Microminiature Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galeria - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stockmann - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vladimirskaya Church - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vosstaniya Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bread Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beloselsky-Belozersky Palace - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anichkov Bridge - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nash Theater - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loft Project Etagi - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anichkov Palace - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oktyabrskiy Big Concert Hall - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Museum of Theatre and Music - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Helvetia Hotel is St. Petersburg (LED-Pulkovo) - 15.4 km / 9.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for TOP Helvetia Hotel St Petersburg is St. Petersburg (LED-Pulkovo) - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="372672663-0"><Room><RoomType code="1002470" text="Double Classic" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="201.60" /><Guests><Adult id="-429496731" first="" last=""><Price amt="100.80" /></Adult><Adult id="-429496732" first="" last=""><Price amt="100.80" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-06-17T00:00:00"><Amount amt="201.60" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-06-22T00:00:00"><Amount amt="201.60" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="372672663-1"><Room><RoomType code="1002213" text="Double Superior" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="253.25" /><Guests><Adult id="-429496733" first="" last=""><Price amt="126.62" /></Adult><Adult id="-429496734" first="" last=""><Price amt="126.63" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-06-17T00:00:00"><Amount amt="253.25" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-06-22T00:00:00"><Amount amt="253.25" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>