<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="370797703_55345"><Hotel id="55345" name="DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel London - Westminster" type="Hotel" stars="4" rank="1"><Region id="52928" name="Westminster &amp; Victoria " /><Address><Address1>30 John Islip Street</Address1><Address2>Westminster</Address2><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW1P 4DD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-207-6301000</Tel><Fax>44-207-72337575</Fax></Address><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>264</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>264</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>264</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/LON-CIT6hotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel London - Westminster is in the heart of London, walking distance from Tate Britain and Lambeth Bridge. This 4-star hotel is close to Big Ben and London Eye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 460 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Computers, complimentary wireless Internet access, and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 460 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Computers, complimentary wireless Internet access, and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel London - Westminster is in the heart of London, walking distance from Tate Britain and Lambeth Bridge. This 4-star hotel is close to Big Ben and London Eye. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tate Britain - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lambeth Bridge - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lambeth Palace - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Tower - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vauxhall Bridge - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Houses of Parliament - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Elizabeth II Conference Centre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westminster Abbey - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parliament Square - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Ben - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westminster Cathedral - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westminster Bridge - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Thomas' Hospital - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cabinet War Rooms - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Florence Nightingale Museum - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 22.5 km / 14 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel London - Westminster is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="370797703-0"><Room><RoomType code="7379479" text="Double Deluxe Room + Free Wifi" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="2285.55" /><Guests><Adult id="-286331154" first="" last=""><Price amt="1142.78" /></Adult><Adult id="-286331155" first="" last=""><Price amt="1142.77" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee><Amount amt="2285.55" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages><Message><Type>Supplier Notes</Type><Text>Important notices: In case of any amendment please contact us to check the rates and conditions as these could change - Hotel will invoice the total amount of this booking in case of no show / En caso de modificacion, por favor contacten con nosotros para verificar las tarifas y condiciones de la reserva ya que podrian ser diferentes - En caso de no show el hotel se reserva el derecho de aplicar gastos del 100%&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</Text></Message></Messages><CancellationPolicyStatus>NonRefundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>