<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="350594403_31262"><Hotel id="31262" name="Four Points by Sheraton Surrey" type="Hotel" stars="3" rank="1"><Region id="31044" name="Surrey" /><Address><Address1>10410 158 St</Address1><Address2 /><City>Surrey</City><State>BC</State><Zip>V4N5C2</Zip><Country>Canada</Country><Tel>1-604-9304700</Tel><Fax>1-604-9304702</Fax></Address><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>355</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>22261</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2283</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bedroom_1.jpg</Url><Width>355</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>13683</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bedroom_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1776</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bedroom_2.jpg</Url><Width>355</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>15374</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bedroom_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1877</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bathroom_1.jpg</Url><Width>355</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>14415</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/SURY-RAM1hotel_Bathroom_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1873</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Four Points by Sheraton Surrey, you'll be centrally located in Surrey, convenient to Guilford Town Centre and Central City Shopping Centre.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Holland Park and Guildford Golf and Country Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 77 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Four Points by Sheraton Surrey. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and express check-out. This hotel has 2 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM   &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Four Points by Sheraton Surrey. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 77 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Four Points by Sheraton Surrey, you'll be centrally located in Surrey, convenient to Guilford Town Centre and Central City Shopping Centre.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Holland Park and Guildford Golf and Country Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Guilford Town Centre - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Central City Shopping Centre - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holland Park - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guildford Golf and Country Club - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red Robinson Show Theatre - 5.2 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bear Creek Park - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surrey Arts Centre - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boulevard Casino - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surrey Golf Club - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northview Golf and Country Club - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pitt Meadows Arena Complex - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meadow Gardens Golf Course - 8.8 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cloverdale Milennium Amphitheatre - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Langley Sportsplex - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Irving House - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Four Points by Sheraton Surrey is Vancouver, BC (YVR-Vancouver Intl.) - 28.6 km / 17.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Coast Surrey Guildford Hotel is Vancouver, BC (YVR-Vancouver Intl.) - 28.6 km / 17.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="350594403-0"><Room><RoomType code="1002038" text="Suite Executive" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="971.36" /><Guests><Adult id="-1073741825" first="" last=""><Price amt="485.68" /></Adult><Adult id="-1073741826" first="" last=""><Price amt="485.68" /></Adult></Guests><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Unknown</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>