<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="370515541_225334639"><Hotel id="225334639" name="Holiday Inn Express Moscow - Sheremetyevo Airport" type="Hotel" stars="3" rank="1"><Region id="140587505" name="Sheremetyevo Airport" /><Address><Address1>SHEREMETYEVO AIRPORT MEZHDUNARODNOE SHOSSE</Address1><City>MOSCOW</City><Zip /><Country>Russia</Country><Tel>7-495-7772660</Tel></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Modern hotel in Moscow Sheremetyevo International Airport (SVO) with an all-day cafe/bar, free Wi-Fi and free inclusive breakfast. Holiday Inn Express Moscow - Sheremetyevo Airport is ideally located only 7 minutes' walk from Sheremetyevo International Airport and from the AeroExpress Train Terminal which will take you directly to Moscow city centre in just 35 minutes every half an hour. In our beautiful and modern design hotel with 198 rooms, begin your day with the inclusive Express Start Breakfast buffet, offering a selection of hot and continental food. The bright and airy Lobby and Bar area is a stylish spot to meet with colleagues or relax with friends after a long flight or while waiting to take-off. Or if you're feeling peckish, order a delicious hot meal or snack from the bar menu in our Express Cafe and Bar and stay in touch with family and friends thanks to free Wi-Fi throughout the hotel. We welcome you to the Holiday Inn Express Moscow - Sheremetyevo Airport and hope that you have a great stay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Holiday Inn Express Moscow - Sheremetyevo Airport is ideally located only 7 minutes' walk from Sheremetyevo International Airport and from the AeroExpress Train Terminal which will take you directly to Moscow city centre in just 35 minutes every half an hour.</Text></Description><Amenity><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="370515541-0"><Room><RoomType code="3344570" text="Room Standard" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="1401.50" /><Guests><Adult id="-2" first="" last=""><Price amt="700.75" /></Adult><Adult id="-3" first="" last=""><Price amt="700.75" /></Adult></Guests><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Unknown</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="370515541-1"><Room><RoomType code="1181507" text="DOUBLE WITH DOUBLE BED" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="1401.50" /><Guests><Adult id="-4" first="" last=""><Price amt="700.75" /></Adult><Adult id="-5" first="" last=""><Price amt="700.75" /></Adult></Guests><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Unknown</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>