<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="390629679_315203529"><Hotel id="315203529" name="Carlow One" type="Hotel" stars="4" rank="1"><Region id="52890" name="Kings Cross &amp; Camden" /><Address><Address1>Carlow Street ,  London</Address1><City>London</City><Zip>NW1 7BS</Zip><Country>England</Country></Address><GeneralInfo /><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="390629679-0"><Room><RoomType code="64243352" text="Executive Suite Apartment (Double)" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="997.57" /><Guests><Adult id="-2" first="" last=""><Price amt="498.78" /></Adult><Adult id="-3" first="" last=""><Price amt="498.79" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee><Amount amt="997.57" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages><Message><Type>Supplier Notes</Type><Text>Essential Information: Room 1&lt;br/&gt;  Hotel Tariff Notes:  A security deposit of GBP 300 is required on arrival via credit card. The deposit is fully refundable upon check-out and subject to a damage inspection of the accommodation.   This property doesn’t accept cash for payment.  This building has no reception. Please contact the property with your arrival time at the apartment so a representative can meet and welcome you personally upon arrival.   The apartments are non-smoking and a fines are applied to guests breaking this rule.   This property has a strict no party, no gathering policy. If there is evidence of a party or gathering, security and/or the police will be called and the apartment will need to be vacated and a penalty of GBP 2000 will be charged.   Late arrivals: Check-in after 23:00 have a surplus charge of GBP 50. There is a standard waiting time of up to 2 hours once the property have received your arrival time, if you don’t arrive after 2 hours of your schedule time there will be a surplus charge of GBP 100, regardless of&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</Text></Message></Messages><CancellationPolicyStatus>NonRefundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>