<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="396395652_10850122"><Hotel id="10850122" name="Beech Mount Hotel" type="Hotel" stars="3" rank="1"><Region id="52609" name="Liverpool" /><Address><Address1>1-3 Beech Street</Address1><Address2 /><City>Liverpool</City><State /><Zip>L7 0HL</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+441512649189</Tel></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Beech Mount Hotel in Liverpool, you'll be minutes from Wavertree Botanic Gardens and close to Liverpool ONE. This hotel is within close proximity of Liverpool City Church and Royal Liverpool University Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request refrigerators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, a safe deposit box at the front desk, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request refrigerators.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Beech Mount Hotel in Liverpool, you'll be minutes from Wavertree Botanic Gardens and close to Liverpool ONE. This hotel is within close proximity of Liverpool City Church and Royal Liverpool University Hospital. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wavertree Botanic Gardens - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool City Church - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Liverpool University Hospital - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Williamson Tunnels Heritage Centre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Liverpool - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool Metropolitan Cathedral - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Everyman Theatre - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;CoverStar Experiences - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Philharmonic Hall - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Unity Theatre - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;O2 Academy - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool Empire Theatre - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princes Road Synagogue - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Static Gallery - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greek Orthodox Church of St Nicholas - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Beech Mount Hotel is Liverpool (LPL-John Lennon) - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Beech Mount Executive Accommodation is Liverpool (LPL-John Lennon) - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="396395652-0"><Room><RoomType code="1002196" text="Double Standard" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="68.07" /><Guests><Adult id="-2" first="" last=""><Price amt="34.04" /></Adult><Adult id="-3" first="" last=""><Price amt="34.03" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-08-18T00:00:00"><Amount amt="68.07" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-08-20T00:00:00"><Amount amt="68.07" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="396395652-1"><Room><RoomType code="1002008" text="Twin Standard" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="77.08" /><Guests><Adult id="-4" first="" last=""><Price amt="38.54" /></Adult><Adult id="-5" first="" last=""><Price amt="38.54" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-08-18T00:00:00"><Amount amt="77.08" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-08-20T00:00:00"><Amount amt="77.08" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="396395652-2"><Room><RoomType code="1002196" text="Double Standard" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="82.48" /><Guests><Adult id="-6" first="" last=""><Price amt="41.24" /></Adult><Adult id="-7" first="" last=""><Price amt="41.24" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-08-18T00:00:00"><Amount amt="82.48" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-08-20T00:00:00"><Amount amt="82.48" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="396395652-3"><Room><RoomType code="1002008" text="Twin Standard" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="91.79" /><Guests><Adult id="-8" first="" last=""><Price amt="45.90" /></Adult><Adult id="-9" first="" last=""><Price amt="45.89" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee from="2019-08-18T00:00:00"><Amount amt="91.79" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-08-20T00:00:00"><Amount amt="91.79" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Refundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>