<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="381035222_33338"><Hotel id="33338" name="Salamanca Terraces" type="Hotel" stars="4" rank="1"><Region id="20229" name="Hobart City" /><Address><Address1>93 Salamanca Place</Address1><Address2 /><City>Battery Point</City><State>TS</State><Zip>7000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-3-62323900</Tel><Fax>61-3-62240112</Fax></Address><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Exterior_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Exterior_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Bedroom_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><ThumbnailUrl>http://api.stuba.com/RXLImages/7/HBA-SAL1hotel_Bedroom_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Salamanca Terraces in Battery Point (Sullivan's Cove), you'll be minutes from Salamanca Place and Salamanca Market.  This 4-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Hobart Function and Conference Centre and Mona Ferry Terminal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 25 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and a computer station. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 25 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Salamanca Terraces in Battery Point (Sullivan's Cove), you'll be minutes from Salamanca Place and Salamanca Market.  This 4-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Hobart Function and Conference Centre and Mona Ferry Terminal. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Salamanca Place - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Salamanca Market - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Function and Conference Centre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mona Ferry Terminal - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parliament House - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Narryna Heritage Museum - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mawson's Huts Replica Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lark Distillery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. George's Anglican Church - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constitution Dock - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maritime Museum of Tasmania - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Wharf - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Town Hall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. David's Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Salamanca Terraces is Hobart, TAS (HBA-Hobart Intl.) - 15 km / 9.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="381035222-0"><Room><RoomType code="1001636" text="Studio Standard" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="737.87" /><Guests><Adult id="-2" first="" last=""><Price amt="368.94" /></Adult><Adult id="-3" first="" last=""><Price amt="368.93" /></Adult></Guests><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Unknown</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result><Result id="381035222-1"><Room><RoomType code="1014037" text="Apartment One Bedroom" /><MealType code="1000041" text="Room only" /><Price amt="854.84" /><Guests><Adult id="-4" first="" last=""><Price amt="427.42" /></Adult><Adult id="-5" first="" last=""><Price amt="427.42" /></Adult></Guests><Messages /><CancellationPolicyStatus>Unknown</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>