<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><AvailabilitySearchResult xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><Currency>GBP</Currency><Warning>
</Warning><TestMode>false</TestMode><HotelAvailability hotelQuoteId="347761758_13460275"><Hotel id="13460275" name="Hotel San Luca" type="Hotel" stars="3" rank="1"><Region id="21076" name="Venice" /><Address><Address1>San Marco 4671 - Calle Dei Fabbri</Address1><Address2 /><City>Venice</City><State /><Zip>30124</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 041 2960833</Tel></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located in San Marco, Hotel San Luca is a perfect starting point from which to explore Venice. Offering a variety of facilities and services, the hotel provides all you need for a good night's sleep. 24-hour front desk, 24-hour room service, facilities for disabled guests, express check-in/check-out, luggage storage are on the list of things guests can enjoy. Comfortable guestrooms ensure a good night's sleep with some rooms featuring facilities such as non smoking rooms, air conditioning, heating, wake-up service, desk. The hotel offers various recreational opportunities. Discover all Venice has to offer by making Hotel San Luca your base. &lt;br/&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Located in San Marco, Hotel San Luca is a perfect starting point from which to explore Venice. Offer &lt;br/&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating></Hotel><Result id="347761758-0"><Room><RoomType code="3988174" text="Double/twin (2 pers)" /><MealType code="1" text="Breakfast" /><Price amt="680119.44" /><Guests><Adult id="-2" first="" last=""><Price amt="340059.72" /></Adult><Adult id="-3" first="" last=""><Price amt="340059.72" /></Adult></Guests><CanxFees><Fee><Amount amt="680119.44" /></Fee><Fee from="2019-04-11T08:19:53.2319041+01:00"><Amount amt="680119.44" /></Fee></CanxFees><Messages><Message><Type>Supplier Notes</Type><Text>IL CHECK-IN PER LA CAMERA ANNEXO DEVE ESSERE FATTO NELL EDIFICIO PRINCIPALE   EL CHECK-IN DE LA HABITACION ANNEXO DEBE SER HECHO EN EL EDIFICIO PRINCIPAL   CITY TAX NO INCLUIDA EN EL PRECIO PAGO DIRECTO EN EL HOTEL POR PERSONA Y NOCHETASSA DI SOGGIORNO NO INCLUSA NEL PREZZO PAGO DIRETTO NELL HOTEL PER PERSONA  E NOTTE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cancelaciones hasta una hora despues de la confirmacion sin gastos. CANCELLATIONS MADE UP TO ONE HOUR AFTER CONFIRMATION, CAN BE MADE FREE OF CHARGE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</Text></Message></Messages><CancellationPolicyStatus>NonRefundable</CancellationPolicyStatus></Room></Result></HotelAvailability></AvailabilitySearchResult>